citymetric.com 2017-12-29

# Privacy policy | CityMetric

At Timetric, we are dedicated to safeguarding and preserving your privacy when visiting our site or communicating electronically with us.

This Privacy Policy, together with our terms of use, provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you.

This Policy is updated from time to time so please review this Policy regularly.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 our data controller is World Market Intelligence Ltd.

World Market Intelligence Ltd is subject to the UK Data Protection Act 1998 and is registered in the UK with the Information Commissioner to process your personal information.

**Information We Collect:**

In operating our website we may collect and process the following data about you:

i. Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs, IP address, operating system, access times, what browser you are using and other communication data.

ii. A number of websites within our group of companies, subsidiaries, related companies and affiliates are tracked using Google Analytics and WebTrends. To view their respective privacy policies and details on opting out, please use the following links:  
- <http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/tos.html>  
- <http://ondemand.webtrends.com/privacypolicy.asp#psfv>

iii. Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website, such as when you register for information or make a purchase.

iv. Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.

**Use Of Your Information**  
The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:

i. To provide you with information requested from us, relating to our products or services. To provide information on other products or services within our group of companies, subsidiaries, related companies and affiliates, which we feel may be of interest to you.

ii. To meet our contractual commitments to you.

iii. To notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or service/product changes, that may affect our service.

iv. Personalise your experience.

If you are a previous or existing customer, we may contact you with information about products and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

Furthermore, we may use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, so that you can be provided with information about unrelated products and services which we consider may be of interest to you. We or they may contact you about these products and services by any methods that you consented at the time your information was collected.

You may stop these messages at any time by emailing [privacypolicy@timetric.com](mailto:privacypolicy@timetric.com) or opting-out using the opt-out tool at the bottom of the email communication.

**Information About Other People**  
On certain parts of the website, you can submit information about other people. For example, you may be able to provide an email address of colleagues who may be interested in registering to attend an event. We will use this information to contact these people for the purposes of increasing event attendance.

These messages can be stopped at any time by emailing [privacypolicy@timetric.com](mailto:privacypolicy@timetric.com) or opting-out using the opt-out tool at the bottom of the email communication.

**Chat and Message Boards**  
A number of websites within our group of companies, subsidiaries, related companies and affiliates offer chat and message boards. Please be advised that information posted in these venues may become public knowledge.

**Storing Your Personal Data**  
We may transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European EconomicArea for processing and storing. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the European Economic Area who work for us or for one of our suppliers. For example, such staff maybe engaged in the processing and concluding of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all reasonable steps to make sure that your data is treated securely and in agreement with this Privacy Policy.  
Data that is provided to us is stored on our secure servers. Details relating to any transactions entered into on our site will be encrypted to ensure its safety.

The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password so that you can access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.

**Disclosing Your Information**  
Where applicable, we may disclose your personal and non-personal information to any member of our group. This includes, where applicable, subsidiaries, related companies or affiliates.

We may also disclose your personal and non-personal information to third parties:

i. Where we sell any or all of our business and/or our assets to a third party.

ii. Where we are legally required to disclose your information.

iii. To assist fraud protection and minimise credit risk.

**Third Party Links**  
The websites contains hyperlinks to websites owned and operated by third parties. These third party websites have their own privacy policies, including cookies, and we urge you to review them. They will govern the use of personal information you submit or are collected by cookies whilst visiting these websites. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third party websites and your use of such websites is at your own risk.

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult their privacy policies.

<http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx>

<http://www.mediaplex.com/mojo_privacy_statement.shtml>

<http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

**Children**  
Please note that we do not collect any personal information from children under thirteen years of age and that no child under thirteen should submit any personal information to any of the Sites. Should we discover that any such personal information has been delivered to any of the Sites, we will remove that information as soon as possible.

**Access To Information**  
The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access the information that we hold about you. Please note that any demand for access may be subject to payment of a fee of £10 which covers our costs in providing you with the information requested. Should you wish to receive details that wehold about you please contact us using the contact details below.

**Use of Cookies**  
On occasion, we may gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website to our advertisers.

Such information will not identify you personally it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.

Similarly to the above, we may gather information about your general internet use by using a cookie file. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you.

All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website.

Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.

**How Timetric Uses Cookies**

Whenever you use our website, information may be collected through the use of cookies and similar technologies. By using Timetric’s websites you agree to the use of cookies as described in this Cookie Policy.

**What Are Cookies?**

Cookies are small text files which are downloaded to your computer or mobile device when you visit a website or application. Your web browser (such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox or Google Chrome) then sends these cookies back to the website or application on each subsequent visit so that they can recognise you and remember things like personalised details or user preferences.

Cookies are referred to as session or persistent cookies, depending on how long they are used:

i. Session cookies only last for your online session and disappear from your computer or device when you close your browser.

ii. Persistent cookies stay on your computer or device after the browser has been closed and last for the period of time specified in the cookie. These persistent cookies are activated each time you visit the site where the cookie was generated.

**What Cookies Does Timetric Use And Why?**

When you use our Websites, the following categories of cookies may be used:

1\. "Strictly necessary" cookies

These cookies are essential in helping you to move around our websites and use their features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies, services you have asked for cannot be provided. These cookies do not gather information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you've been on the internet. These cookies are session cookies, and will be destroyed when you logout of the website or close your browser.

2\. Performance cookies

These cookies aren’t essential but they provide us with useful anonymous information about how people use our website. These cookies cannot be used to identify you as they never contain personal information such as your name or email address. These cookies are persistent.

**How Can You Control Cookies?**

You can always delete existing cookies or change your settings to prevent new cookies being set. Note that if you remove cookies that are “strictly necessary”, this may result in a severely degraded service.

Cookies can be controlled by your browser settings; please see <http://aboutcookies.org/> for more information including a [full guide on how to disable cookies for all major browsers](http://aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1).

**Cookies Set By Third Parties**

We may occasionally use a number of social media tools or external applications to enhance your interaction with this website - for example, we sometimes embed videos from YouTube. As a result, you may be sent cookies from these third party websites. We do not control these cookies and we suggest you check these third party websites for more information about the cookies they use. Please also see [How can you control cookies](https://timetric.com/about/cookie-policy/#cookie-control) above for guidance on how you can switch off or delete cookies on other websites.

**Contacting Us**  
We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. Please do not hesitate to contact us at: [privacypolicy@timetric.com](mailto:privacypolicy@timetric.com)

POST: Data Team, World Market Intelligence Ltd, John Carpenter House, John Carpenter Street,London, EC4Y 0AN, UK
